[{"front":"The Atlantic Ocean is on the east coast of the United States.","back":"Atlantics Ocean"},
    {"front":"The Speaker of the House becomes president if both the President and Vice President can no longer serve.","back":"Speaker of the House"},
    {"front":"George Washington is the Father of Our Country.","back":"George Washington"},
    {"front":"Benjamin Franklin was the first Postmaster General of the United States.","back":"Benjamin Franklin"},
    {"front":"Franklin Roosevelt was President during the Great Depression and World War II.","back":"Franklin Roosevelt"},
    {"front":"There are 100 U.S Senators.","back":"Senators"},
    {"front":"The Bill of Rights is the first ten amendments to the Constitution.","back":"Bill of Rights"},
    {"front":"The President is in charge of the executive branch.","back":"President"},
    {"front":"Paul Ryan is the current Speaker of the House of Representatives.","back":"Paul Ryan"},
    {"front":"The House of Representatives has 435 voting members","back":"435"}]